[
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Recorded by American singer Kesha, which of these songs debuted at number one in 2010?",
    "choice1": "We R Who We R",
    "choice2": "Blah Blah Blah",
    "choice3": "Die Young",
    "choice4": "Take it Off",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which of these Beatles' albums was the first to be released?",
    "choice1": "Hard Day's Night",
    "choice2": "With The Beatles",
    "choice3": "Beatles for Sale",
    "choice4": "Please Please Me",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Released on the 2013 album Bangerz, which American artist had a hit with the song \"We Can't Stop\"?",
    "choice1": "Katy Perry",
    "choice2": "Miley Cyrus",
    "choice3": "Carrie Underwood",
    "choice4": "Taylor Swift",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which pop star was married to film actress Sandra Dee from 1960 to 1967?",
    "choice1": "Duane Eddy",
    "choice2": "Bobby Darin",
    "choice3": "Elvis Presley",
    "choice4": "Buddy Holly",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Stronger, released in 2011, is the fifth studio album by which female pop star?",
    "choice1": "Pink",
    "choice2": "Beyonce",
    "choice3": "Kelly Clarkson",
    "choice4": "Taylor Swift",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which 1960s English band was fronted by singer Eric Burdon?",
    "choice1": "The Kinks",
    "choice2": "The Rolling Stones",
    "choice3": "The Animals",
    "choice4": "The Beatles",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Released in 1983, who sang with Kenny Rogers on the duet \"We've Got Tonight\"?",
    "choice1": "Sheena Easton",
    "choice2": "Olivia Newton-John",
    "choice3": "Dolly Parton",
    "choice4": "Kim Carnes",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Originally by Elvis Presley, who had a hit with \"Can't Help Falling in Love\" in 1993?",
    "choice1": "U2",
    "choice2": "Simply Red",
    "choice3": "UB40",
    "choice4": "Simple Minds",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Performed by Jimi Hendrix at the Monterey Pop Festival in 1967, who originally recorded the song \"Wild Thing\"?",
    "choice1": "The Troggs",
    "choice2": "The Animals",
    "choice3": "The Zombies",
    "choice4": "The Wild Ones",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a song recorded by the rock band \"Nirvana\"?",
    "choice1": "Come as You Are",
    "choice2": "Everlong",
    "choice3": "The Man Who Sold the World",
    "choice4": "Lithium",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which of the following bands was the first to be inducted into the Rock 'n' Roll Hall of Fame?",
    "choice1": "ZZ Top",
    "choice2": "Genesis",
    "choice3": "The Hollies",
    "choice4": "Metallica",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Known as the Killer, what instrument does American musician Jerry Lee Lewis play?",
    "choice1": "Drums",
    "choice2": "Piano",
    "choice3": "Guitar",
    "choice4": "Trumpet",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "The American band Blondie was founded in 1974 by guitarist Chris Stein and lead singer...",
    "choice1": "Kim Wilde",
    "choice2": "Chrissie Hynde",
    "choice3": "Debbie Harry",
    "choice4": "Debbie Gibson",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which all-female band's studio albums include Beauty and the Beat, Vacation and Talk Show?",
    "choice1": "The Bangles",
    "choice2": "Bananarama",
    "choice3": "The Runaways",
    "choice4": "The Go-Go's",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which of these Bob Dylan albums was the first to be released?",
    "choice1": "Highway 61 Revisited",
    "choice2": "John Wesley Harding",
    "choice3": "Blonde on Blonde",
    "choice4": "The Freewheelin' Bob Dylan",
    "answer": 4
  }
]